A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art AAA.finccoll
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1958-1975; Series 2; 2.2 Linear feet Boxes 3-4, 22, OV 23
  - General (Box 3)
    - Jeff Dell and Jeff Dell Film Service (Box 3)
      - "Dodge City", ca. 1967; 1 Film reels 16 mm (Box 3, Folder 35, Item 1)
      - "Hush Hush Sweet City", undated; 1 Film reels Leader also labeled "Bob Monroe" 16 mm (Box 3, Folder 35, Item 2)
      - "Happy Birthday Felisa", 1968; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) Duplicate; 1 Videocassettes (Digital Betacam) Duplicate; 1 Film reels Original 16 mm (Box 3, Folder 36)
        Videocassettes are duplicate access copies of original motion picture film. Original film reel stored off-site.
    - Agnes Denes, circa 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      Contains letters, descriptions of artworks, photocopied typescript theoretical writings, clippings, and press releases.
    - Jim Dine, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Pat Diska, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      Contains letters and a sketch by the artist
    - Seena Donneson, 1966, 1967, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      Oversized poster housed in OV 23.
    - Jacob Drachler, circa 1966 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Josef Drapell, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Jean Dubuffet, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Dale Eldred, circa 1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Ahron Elvaiah, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Jules Engel, circa 1968 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Frances Field, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Helen Frankenthaler, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Charles Frazier, circa 1965 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      Contains photocopied typescript, "Excerpts from a work journal on flying sculpture"
    - Sue Fuller, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Paul Gedeohn, circa 1966-1974 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Paul George, circa 1968 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Robert Goodnough, circa 1973 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Adolph Gottlieb, circa 1970 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Gertrude Greene, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Stephen Greene, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Dorothy Greene-Pepper, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      Contains correspondence and typescript entitled "Instructions for the care of molded cloth sculptures."
    - Nancy Grossman, circa 1969 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Group of Six, circa 1972 (Box 3, Folder 59-61)
      Contains slides, photos, resumes, and published material from Stephen Greene, Phoebe Helman, Richard Stankiewicz, Richard Miller, Anthonyh Padovano, Charles Cajori, and Lennart Anderson, as well as a letter proposing an exhibition
    - Aaronel De Roy Gruber, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 62)
      Contains correspondence, clippings, slides, photographs, printed material, and a reference statement written by Elayne Varian
    - Lee Hall, circa 1968 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Irene Hamar, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Hiroshi Hattori, circa 1969 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Eva Hesse, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      Oversized magazine article housed in box 22, folder 2
    - Dick Higgins, 1968 April (Box 3, Folder 67)
      Contains "Something Else Newsletter," 1968 April
    - Charles Hinman, circa 1964 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Theo Hios, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Raymond Hitchcock, 1967, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 70)
      Contains correspondence and photographs of artwork; also a letter and photographs from Harry Weisburd
    - Frederic Hobbs, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Gerrit Hondius, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Budd Hopkins, circa 1969 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Nelson Howe, 1964-1971 (Box 3, Folder 74)
      Contains letters
    - Ralph Humphrey, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Richard Hunt, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Neil Jenney, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Ray Johnson, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 78)
      Contains mail art, clippings, letters, and photocopied writings
    - Allen Jones, circa 1964 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - George Bobby Jones, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Jacques Kaplan, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 82)
      Contains correspondence and clippings regarding "Fur Show"
    - Fredric Karoly, circa 1964 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Lila Katzen, 1969-1975 (Box 3, Folder 84)
      Contains clippings, press releases, photographs, and slides
    - Emily Kenas, circa 1965 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Elena Kepalas, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Justin Knowles, circa 1966 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Sacha Kolin, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 88)
      Contains correspondence regarding gifts and works on loan to the museum
    - Joseph Kosuth, circa 1967 (Box 3, Folder 89)
      Contains photographs of artworks
    - Kristen Kraa, circa 1964 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Yayoi Kusama, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 91)
      Contains a letter from the artist
    - Gerald Laing, circa 1964 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Ellen Lanyon, circa 1962 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Charles Lassiter, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Leonid, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Josef Levi, circa 1966 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Les Levine, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 97)
      Contains clippings, press releases, photographs, printed material, and poster. Oversized poster and magazine housed in OV 23.
    - John Loring, circa 1967 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Sven Lukin, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Howard Mehring, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Carlos Merida, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - D.M. Merrick, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Michael Metz, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Evelyn Metzger, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Ursula Meyer, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Toto Meylon, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Jay Milder, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Guido Molinari, circa 1964 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Molla, undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Symcho Moszkowicz, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 110)
      Contains photographs of the artist
    - Don Nice, circa 1964 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Isamu Noguchi, circa 1967 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Earl Olsen, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - George Ortwin, circa 1971 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Bruce Nauman, circa 1970 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Alfonso Ossorio, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Anthony Padovano, 1960-1972 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Barbara Phillips Perle, circa 1974 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - William Pettet, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Bernard Pfreim, 1967, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 119)
      Oversized poster housed in OV 23
  - General (Box 4)
    - Pablo Picasso, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Lil Picard, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Contains letters and photocopied writings
    - Roberto Pignataro, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Contains slides.
    - Paul Pollaro, 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Thomas Prentiss, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Raquel Rabinovich, circa 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Edward Randel, circa 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Contains instructions and technical information about light/motion work "Hegira"
    - Antonio Recalcati, circa 1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Odilon Redon, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Philip Reisman, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Jeanne Reynal, circa 1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - James Ridlon, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Bridget Riley, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Esther Rolick, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Seymour Rosenthal, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Oversized poster in OV 23
    - Stephen Rosenthal, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Contains correspondence, photographs, and a typescript artist's statement
    - James Russell, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Graham Redgrave Rust, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Freida Savitz, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Joseph Schillinger, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Contains correspondence with Schillinger's widow, Frances Schillinger
    - Miriam Schapiro, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Roslyn Schomer, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Theresa Schwartz, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Contains a letter, photographs, and a magazine article
    - James Seawright, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Roger Selchow, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Contains correspondence
    - Thomas Sills, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Arlie Sinaiko, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Esther Forman Singer, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Richard Smith, circa 1971 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Tony Smith, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Contains photographs of installation
    - Robert Smithson, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Alan Sondheim, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Jack Sonenberg, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Harry Soviak, 1964-1971 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Norma Jeas Squires, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      Contains photographs
    - Sala Staw, circa 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Harold Stevenson, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Risa (Rissa Sussman), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      Contains correspondence, contact sheets and instructions for dismantling sculpture
    - Joan Tausik, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Helen Thomas, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - George Tooker, circa 1964 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Anthony Tortora, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Cy Twombly, circa 1970 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Stella Waitzkin, circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Judy Waterman, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Jeanne Whorrall, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - John Wilde, circa 1963 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - John Willenbacher, 1964-1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      Contains letter from the artist. Oversized poster housed in box 22, folder 2.
    - Neil Williams, circa 1964 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - New York Arts Calendar Annual (Box 4)
    - Letter Describing Donation of Artist Files, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Antonakos - Elliott, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      Also contains a form for the artist Leonid
    - McAfee - McNeill, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Meigs - Mieczkowski, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Miller - Mitchell, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Model - Morang, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Morera - Muelller, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Muhl - Nagare, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Nachumi - Nelson, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Neujean - Noyer, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Okada - Oxtoby, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Parker - Pattison, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Pereira - Phillips, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Pickhardt - Pitigliani, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Pollack - Quirt, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Radulovic - Reder, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Reed - Rodin, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Rodriguez - Rosso, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Rothbort - Ryman, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Ssaleme - Sawyer, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Schaeffer - Schneider, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Schoener - Seley, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Seliger - Schurr, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Schwartz - Sheppard, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Scherbeck - Simpson, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Solotaire - Spiro, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Spoerri - Stefanelli, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Stern - Streeter, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Subirachs - Swinson, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Oversized Poster, Maggy Aldrich, from box 3, folder 6, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Exhibition Catalog, Henryk Berlewi from box 3, folder 14, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Poster, Enrique Castro-Cid from box 3, folder 24, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Clippings, Doris Chase, from box 3, folder 25, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Poster, George Cohen, from box 3, folder 30, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Magazine Article, Eva Hesse, from box 3, folder 66, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Poster, John Willenbacher, from box 4, folder 48, circa 1964 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Poster and Clippings, Sylvia Carewe, from box 3, folder 22, 1959-1968 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Poster, Jaime Davidovich, from box 3, folder 34, 1973 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Poster, Seena Donneson, from box 3, folder 40, 1966 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Poster and Magazine, Les Levine, from box 3, folder 97, 1968-1969 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Poster, Bernard Pfreim, from box 3, folder 120, 1967 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Poster, Seymour Rosenthal, from box 4, folder 15, 1966 (Box OV 23)
- Elayne Varian Personal Papers, 1965-1970; Series 3; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 5-6
  All of the sound recordings in this series have been digitized for research use.
  Series consists of records related to curatorial, teaching, and writing projects of Elayne Varian that were not undertaken in her role at Finch College.
  Curatorial projects include the exhibition Art Today (1967), a juried show at the New York State Fair; a series of art film screenings held at the Everson Museum of Art of Syracuse University, and an exhibition at Guild Hall in East Hampton featuring local artists over the age of 60.
  A single file of teaching materials consists of a syllabus and course schedule.
  The bulk of writings in the series consist of recorded interviews, with corresponding transcripts, of art dealers and artists, which were conducted for a 1970 article Varian wrote for Art in America called "New Dealing," on the subject of artist-dealer relationships. Interviews, listed individually in the folder list, are on 11 sound tape reels and are typically around 40 minutes in duration. Photographs related to that project are also found depicting Virginia Dwan, Martha Jackson, and Leo Castelli with Andy Warhol. Other writing projects include published interviews with artists Brian O'Doherty and Babette Newburger, a manual on museum security, and an article on patented art. The original interview with Newburger is found on one sound tape reel with an edited transcript.
  - Curation outside of Finch College (Box 5)
    - New York State Fair, "Art Today" (1967) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Everson Museum Film Series, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - Guild Hall, "21 Over 60" (1973) (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
  - Teaching, circa 1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Writings
    - Book Review of Arte Povera, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Interview with Brian O'Doherty for Art International, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lecture for Wagner College, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Museum Security, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
    - "New Dealing" for Art in America (1970 Jan)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Interview with Leo Castelli, 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Edited Transcript of Castelli Interview for the Archives of American Art, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Interview with Virginia Dwan, 1969 April; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Interview with John Gibson, circa 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Interview with Richard Feigen, 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Interview with Arnold Glimcher and Fred Mueller of Pace Gallery, 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Interview with Adolph Gottlieb, 1969 May 20; Transcript (Box 5, Folder 20)
        Recording of Gottlieb interview is found on sound tape reel with Charles Ross interview
      - Interview with Martha Jackson, 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Interview with Sidney Janis, 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Interview with Roy Lichtenstein, 1969 May 20; Transcript (Box 5, Folder 23)
        Recording of Lichtenstein interview is found on sound tape reel with Charles Ross interview
      - Interview with Betty Parsons, circa 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Interview with Charles Ross, 1969 May 20; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 25)
        Sound tape reel also contains Gottlieb and Lichtenstein interviews, whose transcripts are filed under their names.
      - Interview with Seth Siegelaub, circa 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - "New Dealing" for Art in America (1970 Jan) (Box 6)
      - Interview with Howard Wise, circa 1969; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Interview Notes, circa 1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Handwritten Drafts, circa 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Typescript Drafts, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Photographs and Captions, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        Contains a negative of a photograph of Virginia Dwan taken by Nancy Smithson, photographs of Martha Jackson with Claire Falkenstein, Paul Jenkins, and Antoni Tapies, and slides of Andy Warhol with Leo Castelli.
      - Research, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Patented Art, 1965, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Contains notes from an interview with Sue Fuller
    - "Plastics for Everyday Living: Babette Newberger" for Art in America (1969 August), 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 6, Folder 8)
      A published interview with Newberger conducted by Elaine Varian
- Exhibition Files, 1943-1975; Series 4; 14.8 Linear feet Boxes 6-22, OV 24-25
  Series is arranged alphabetically by exhibition title, with materials for each exhibition arranged by type. Selected exhibition catalogs are also arranged alphabetically at the beginning of the series. The records of each exhibition are arranged slightly differently, and what arrangement was found is retained, with folder headings sometimes changed for clarity. Additional exhibition files for shows curated by Elayne Varian outside of Finch College are found in series 3, Elayne Varian personal papers.
  All of the sound and video recordings found in this series have been digitized and are available for research use. The motion picture film documenting Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Structure (1966) has also been digitized.
  Series contains records documenting the creation and public exhibition of shows at the Contemporary Wing galleries from its inception in 1964 to its close in 1975, as well as records for several exhibitions that were in development but not yet realized when the college closed. Documentation includes artist files, checklists, correspondence, writings, exhibition catalogs, photographs, interviews, films and videos documenting exhibitions or created for exhibition, artist statements, loan documentation, insurance documentation, and publicity in the form of press releases, exhibition announcements, clippings, and posters. A run of exhibition catalogs filed at the beginning of the series represent about half of the exhibitions held in the Contemporary Wing. Catalogs are also found filed under each exhibition's title for most of the exhibitions in the series, often annotated with insurance values or in various drafts.
  Unlike the artist files in series 2, artist files specific to exhibitions tend to contain richer documentation, including writings and original correspondence with the artist, artist statements, photographs, or information about particular artworks.
  Interviews are found on 9 sound cassettes and 14 sound tape reels scattered in the exhibition files, all conducted by Elayne Varian and relating to the exhibition at hand. They include Alan Sonfist ("Alan Sonfist: Time Landscape"), Mel Bochner ("Art in Process IV), Hans Richter ("Hans Richter Retrospective"), Ruth Richards on Hugo Weber ("Hugo Weber Retrospective), James Brooks and Janet Katz ("James Brooks Retrospective," transcript only), Physicists Lloyd G. Cross, Allyn Z. Lite, and Gerald Thomas Bern Pethick ("N-Dimensional Space), Margaret Benyon ("N-Dimensional Space"), Irwin Hollander (transcript only, "Prints from Hollander's Workshop"), David Anderson ("The Private Collection of Martha Jackson"), Doris Chase ("Projected Art: Artists at Work"), and Will Insley, Michael Kirby, Les Levine, Ursula Meyer, Brian O'Doherty, Charles Ross, and Tony Smith ("Schemata 7"); Douglas Davis, Jane Davis, and Russ Connor ("Talk-Out!"); Les Levine ("The Troubles"); Michael Mazur and Paul Gedeohn ("Two Aspects of An Illusion"). An additional sound recording describing the installation and content of the exhibition "Towers" is found on one sound tape reel.
  In addition to the recorded interviews, a number of moving image recordings are found. The video in Artists' Videotape Performances (1971) is a complex mix of recordings, ranging from simple, single-channel video works that were played in the gallery, to components of multi-channel installations, artifacts of interactive sound and video installations, and recordings of performances put on in the gallery. Other motion pictures found in the series include videos of artists Sam Weiner, Lynda Benglis, and Michael Singer working in Projected Art: Artists at Work (1971), and film of the installed exhibition Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Structure (1966). In total, motion pictures in this series are on 19 videoreels (1/2 inch), 2 film reels (16 mm, with VHS and Digital Betacam videocassette access copies).
  Other artworks or components of artworks found include original writings by Dan Graham in Art in Series (1967-1968) and mail art by Richard Merkin and Ray Johnson in Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Collage (1967). Artists books found in the series include Statements by Lawrence Weiner and Identikit by Jim Brodey, found in Lynda Benglis' artist file; both of these publications are with records for Art in Process IV (1969-1970). Schematic drawings, floor plans, and installation instructions are found for Robert Morris for Art in Process V (1972) Douglas Davis and several other artists for Artists' Videotape Performances (1971), Michael Kirby for Schemata 7 (1967), Stan Vanderbeek for Projected Art (1966-1967), and various works for N-Dimensional Space (1970).
  - Selected Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9-14)
  - "Agnes Denes" (not realized), circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - "Alan Sonfist: Time Landscape" (1975, Not realized at Finch College) (Box 6)
    - Artist File, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correpondence, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Interview with Sonfist, circa 1974; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Project File, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - "American Art Deco Architecture" (1974-1975) (Box 6)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Grant, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, circa 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 22-27)
      Oversized photographs housed in box 22, folder 3
  - "Arshile Gorky Drawings" (not realized), 1967, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - "Art Deco" (1970) (Box 6)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Catalog Drafts, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Oversized galleys housed in box 22, folder 3
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 31-33)
      See also loan documentation for additional correspondence.
    - Insurance, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Lists, circa 1970 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      Oversized lists in box 22, folder 3
    - Loans, 1970 (Box 7)
      - Loan Forms, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 1-9)
      - Outstanding Loan Forms, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Lender Lists, circa 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Peter Brant, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Cooper-Hewitt Museum of Design, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Galerie Sonnabend, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Edward Lee Cave, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Stanley Insler, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Rockwell Kent / Larcada Gallery, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Lillian Nassau, Ltd., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Richard Merkin, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Metropolitan Museum, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
      - Museum of Modern Art, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - John Nicolas Streep, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Barbara Streisand / Sybarites, Inc., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Andy Warhol, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 28)